I will briefly introduce the new features of Marvelous 3rd Anniversary 2020.
After introducing the asset creation update, I will share a case.
In that case, I will introduce more features to you.
The first one is the concept update.
In the new version of Marvelous 3rd Anniversary 2020,
we will update the experience.
First of all, the tool selection and switching will be faster.
Second, the number, the number of characters, and the selection will be more intelligent and convenient.
The UV editor is a main window.
You can switch it in the process of using it.
It will display the UV editor or the 2D window.
In addition,
the UV editor will select the other two windows,
only one window,
and put them together to make it easier to use.
The UV editor adjusts the UV.
On the side,
we will select the elements that will be used in the 3D window.
For example, like the material or the buttons,
you don't need to change them through the title bar.
Now, like our historical window,
the UV editor can be used as the side window.
You can stack and line them up.
Just like the previous update version,
the current line-up and adjustment will be more intelligent and convenient.
And then, like our side windows,
you can put them together.
If you don't want to use them,
you can just display the two main windows.
And then, since we mentioned our interface update,
we have one more thing.
We will update the 2D window.
Because now,
the 2D window and the connection layer
have been combined.
They are now combined into a new asset.
In the new asset,
first of all,
because of our interface update,
when we are selecting these different materials,
as long as you click on the leftmost icon,
you can find the corresponding material.
For example, like the clothing material,
and the virtual model material.
The speed of our new interface is very fast.
For example, in the new version,
we have added some platform models.
These platform models can be used directly.
They also have wearable information.
So you can do it in different clothes.
When it has wearable information,
you can match your model
or the model we have added.
In addition,
we have added these white-patterned
sheets of clothing.
They can be used directly.
They also have wearable information.
After adding these white-patterned sheets of clothing,
we can go to our fabric store.
We have added a lot of new fabrics
and their materials.
We have added them again.
So now,
when we are selecting the fabrics
in the software,
we can go directly to the window of the fabric store
to select these fabrics.
Then we can check the different fabrics
on the virtual model
and the clothing effect.
Including our display type,
we can turn it into detailed information.
This way,
we can quickly switch our materials.
Or we can change its order mode.
For example,
we can change the size of the fabric
according to the size of the fabric.
Or we can change the quality of the fabric.
The adjustment of the asset department
is not only about
the adjustment of these default assets.
It also includes
the addition of some materials
that are like water.
We can use it through the sticker
in Marvel Space 3.
It also includes
our accessories.
In the previous version,
we have some of the accessories
that are available.
For example,
we have the eye-catching eye-catching eye-catching.
Now,
we have a lot of
eye-catching eye-catching eye-catching.
And we have some
of these materials
that are in the current update.
Finally,
we have the scenarios.
Now,
we have added a lot of
scenarios and eye-catching
in Marvel Space 3.
You can directly
use them.
These are the
updates of the asset department
that are in the current update.
There is a new
big update
that is
in the current
online store,
online mall.
When you open it,
you can open
these free files
directly
in the store.
As long as
you are in the online mode,
for example,
we are going to
choose a suitable
costume.
As long as
you burn
this costume,
this costume will
be downloaded
from the background
and opened
in Marvel Space 3.
So,
we don't need
to go to the online page
to download
and buy
and download
it directly.
You can directly
open the costume
in Marvel Space 3
by double-clicking
in the store.
In fact,
it's not just
the costume.
For example,
you can also
directly change
your fabric.
For example,
in my backstage,
in the store,
I selected
a variety of
fabrics.
As long as
I drag
this fabric
into the software
in the store,
I can actually
change the fabric.
So,
now,
our asset department
is not like before.
We don't need
to go to
the official website
to download
and download
it directly.
And we also have
some auxiliary materials,
such as
the neckline
of this
investment neckline
like me.
So,
I can also
drag
the neckline
in the upper left corner
to the corresponding
asset shop
and change it.
Besides these,
you can also
customize
your own asset department
like we have
some common
documents on
your computer.
You can also
add assets
to quickly
download
some of
our existing
clothes.
In addition
to
downloading
the existing
clothes,
we also have
the model
library.
In the previous version,
we actually
also have
the model library.
But in the previous version,
the model library
we use it more often
to quickly
download
the assets
from the
website.
For example,
I can use
the model library
in the previous
version
to find the
corresponding
parts
according to
our
design
of the
clothing
material
and
put them
together.
For example,
I am now
a客
and there is
a model
frame
in the
2D window.
We can
change
the model
frame
and the model
together
to identify
how to
replace
or inherit
the model frame.
So now
we have a set of
clothes
to change
the model
frame.
We can replace
the model
frame
but when
we change the
style,
in the previous version,
it will replace
the model frame
in the background.
It will no longer
inherit the model
frame.
If we need to replace
a single model frame,
we need to replace
the model frame
editor.
But in the new version,
we don't need
to do this anymore.
In the new version,
we have the interface
update.
So now,
even if we want to
replace
different types
or different
clothing
parts,
we can
do it
directly.
In the new version,
we also
added
a model
setting.
Of course,
the model frame
is not only used
to transfer
the original
assets
but also
to replace
your own
assets.
For example,
I have a set
of clothes
to change
the model frame
frame.
I can choose
the model frame
at the bottom
of the model frame.
This is actually
similar to the
previous model frame.
It is also
fast
to make
a big
change.
For example,
when I change
the model frame,
I can change
the model frame
to a new model frame.
This is similar to
the previous model frame.
But in the new model frame,
if we adjust
the version
setting,
for example,
I want to
change the sleeve
to another
style sleeve,
I can re-definition
the sleeve
as a new
sleeve module.
And this sleeve module
can be
replaced
with other
clothing items
at the same time.
As long as I
define it
as a sleeve module,
now we can
change the
design
of the
module.
So,
when we
register
this
to the
model frame,
even if we
change
different
clothing types,
for example,
I want to
change
other
clothing types,
or even
I change
the whole
style
of the
model frame.
For example,
I change
the long-sleeve
top
of the
top,
I change the
length of
the
sleeve,
I change
the length
of the
sleeve,
and I
change the
width of
the
sleeve.
For some
of the
new
designs,
the
next
step
is to
change
the
width
of
the
Then we can create a model of a model drawing, or a model of a model drawing,
and then define a certain part of it into a model.
After we have a new clothing type, we can continue to adjust the parts of each part.
In other words, as long as some of the basics of the model drawing are established in the early stages,
we can divide the costumes that we have made in the past into different models of each part,
just like a lego and a log.
After that, we can try to re-organize the log of these different positions.
In addition to the fact that we can register different positions individually,
we can also use some system templates.
After that, we can change these different parts to match
what they should look like.
We can change these different parts to match what they should look like.
After that, we can change these different parts to match what they should look like.
For example, if we want to match the sleeves and collar to a certain model,
we need to use an intelligent method to select the cloth type for each part.
For example, for the front part, we can put all the pieces of the front part together.
Here, the front part has a pocket, so we have to put the pocket together.
After that, we can register it.
After registration,
The other parts are also adjusted in the same way.
For example, the back is fixed here.
So now we are in the creation of the costume.
Everyone has a little concept with you.
For example, my sleeves are sleeves.
I think when I create it later,
I can fix it first.
So even if I have to replace it later.
For example, after I changed the sleeves,
I don't think the first version is good.
Everyone should understand.
Sometimes I changed it for a long time,
and I found that I still like the first version the most.
At this time, you can find the first version,
and replace it with the first version.
Including the pocket here.
If you want to create a bag pocket,
you can also align the pocket with it first.
After that, when you replace it,
you don't have to do the same thing over and over again.
It's more convenient.
Including the roll-up sleeves.
In fact, sometimes we use the roll-up function.
And also use the symmetrical arrangement.
This function can quickly complete
the symmetrical roll-up of the sleeves on both sides.
In this case,
after we roll up a sleeve,
if we want to replace the sleeves of other versions,
we don't need to roll up or do any other operations.
You can just replace the rolled sleeve
with the one on the clothing.
These are the questions about our clothing assets.
Next, we will go through a...
I want to share with you guys
what other updates we have.
But before that,
I want to tell you guys
how I found this case
when I just showed you
in this case.
First of all,
I'm doing a Hanfu case here.
So I'll go to Connect Shop
to find out if I have any new hair styles.
Here I found a double bowl head.
Of course,
when you make your own files,
you can also go to our Connect Shop
to see if there are any files
that you think are suitable
or if there are any other files
that suit you.
When you make Hanfu,
you have to pay attention to one thing.
Because Hanfu is actually very simple.
It's just that
there are different parts of the style.
So before we make it,
because its pattern is very simple,
you have to pay attention
when you make the assembly
you have to make sure
that you change your pattern
to a T-pose.
This way,
it's easier for you to
deny the value of the pattern
or to wear it.
Instead,
you just have to arrange it.
When I make the 3D hair style,
it's more intuitive
and we can deny it.
Then we can start modeling.
After the modeling,
sometimes we can't see
how loose it is.
In the new version,
we can make the hard-to-read
with the hard-to-read pattern.
For example,
we can measure the color
in the exaggerated position
of its shape.
Or in the previous version,
we used the grid to show
its stretch and deformation.
Now we can use a soft-to-read
or a gradient
or a neutral situation
to show more clearly
which parts
are under more pressure.
Now I can see
there are some tightness
on its chest.
So there are some
thinness under its eyes.
This proves that
we need to adjust
the pattern
in these specific positions.
After we make some adjustments,
we can move on to the next step.
Actually,
when I first started
to build these outfits,
I didn't build them all at once.
Sometimes I would
change the model's posture
and look at it.
I put it down on the T-pose
and put my hand on it.
After putting it down,
it doesn't fit me.
If it fits me,
I will continue
to build my model.
For the high-heels,
although it sounds like
an outfit with a lot of fabric,
in fact,
the pattern is very simple.
The difference is that
sometimes our sleeves
are straight or
a bit narrow,
and the chest might be crossed
or flat,
or straight.
They all have different
types of clothing and effects.
In fact,
they are just a combination
of different parts.
So I choose to use
this one
to complete these outfits.
After I have finished
building these
high-heels,
I might start to
make some changes
or adjustments
to them.
For example,
my front is
a two-sided
pink front.
Now I might
change it
to a cross-sectional front.
If I change it
to a cross-sectional front,
I might hide
both sides
of my front
first,
and then
do some cutting
operations.
The reason why I hide
both sides of my front
is because
I am not sure
how the cutting
will look like.
Also,
the high-heels
might be made
into a jacket,
but most of the time
the jacket
is long.
So I will just
delete the lines
and make it
long.
After that,
I will continue
to make
this cross-sectional front
into a top.
Now I have
two parts
of the front.
One is a cross-sectional
front,
and the other
is a straight
cross-sectional front.
After that,
I only need to
change different
parts
when I
create
different
clothes.
As you can see,
when I change
the parts,
the damage
will continue.
So,
when you
complete
the
previous
material
to a certain
extent,
you can
increase
the number
of clothes
or
the variety
of your
documents.
There is a trick
here.
When you
make the
collar,
don't sew
the sides
together.
Normally,
the front
and the back
of the collar
should be sewn
together.
Sometimes,
it will
affect
the effect
of the
pattern.
Sometimes,
the collar
may have
a gap
or some
holes.
So,
don't
add
any holes
to the collar.
At this time,
if there is
a small problem,
for example,
if there is
a lot of
fabric on the
side,
you can
fix it.
But if you
sew the
collar
at the
beginning,
you may
not know
where to
change
and
how to
sew
it.
Then,
create
the collar
like this
and those
are all
materials
you can
use
to make
the collar
look
more
stylish.
If you
want
to
use
the collar
to make
look
more
stylish,
then
you can
use
the collar
to make
look
more
stylish.
You can speed up the process as I mentioned earlier.
For example, the scale is a little bit different.
It may be a little bit obvious.
Or I just want to try different scale effects.
Then I can define the scale of different lengths and widths into different modules.
Then I can quickly switch the scale.
And see which one works better.
For example, I make the scale a little bit wider.
Then I change the scale again.
To see the effect.
In addition to numbers, there are some other modules.
For example, the scale in the front is a nuclear scale.
Or it is a parallel scale.
Then we can see the difference between the scale in the front and the scale in the back.
And the modules can be modified.
Sometimes,
you just need to
change the scale in the front and the scale in the back.
Or you can adjust the scale in the back.
Then you will see the effect of the whole costume.
Or the texture of the costume you want.
It will be different.
So in our new version,
the new way of designing the costumes
through the defined scale
can help you save a lot of time.
Then we have a number.
We can put it directly into the other modules.
So when we use other modules,
we can also use these blocks.
Then this is a leather-plated sleeve.
The leather-plated sleeve has a sewing circle.
It is just a clarification.
There is a sewing circle on the sleeve,
and there is no sewing circle on the sleeve.
Then we can use the matching arrangement tool
to mix the wrinkles on the other side
with the wrinkles we have adjusted.
Also, the sleeve panel of our simulation can also be directly mixed with the wrinkles.
So you don't need to manually
match the two sleeves.
Then, for example, after I add the wrinkles,
its wrinkles will change.
Then before we simulate,
we will add a shape optimization first.
The shape optimization function
can maintain these wrinkles.
So after we use the shape optimization function,
we will simulate again.
These wrinkles that have been adjusted
will not scatter like before.
We can continue to maintain these wrinkles.
But the shape optimization function
is a function that we often use
when we make this kind of costume
or when we have a lot of fabric.
OK.
So this is the simulation
for our model drawing,
the model drawing of the design.
And then the next new function is
the everywhere function.
The everywhere function is actually
a function that is hard to think of
when it comes to the five-point binding function.
In fact, the five-point binding function
in our model drawing
is hidden in the everywhere function.
But in this case,
in order to make the five-point binding function
a little more convenient,
I will first make the tight clothes
of the type
with shrinkage first
to make it a tight effect,
and then I will make the mango.
In the new version,
we also have an independent display frame.
The display frame can now be passed through
and can be shared with other
clothing display types.
For example,
in the previous version,
you can choose to open the display frame
on the surface of the
and now you can display the frame
in different clothing models,
such as black and white clothing models,
or single color display,
that is, single-sided or single color display.
They can all be shared.
That is to say,
there is a possibility
that we can display the other side of the pattern
while running the machine.
You can make the back side adjustment.
Let's continue to the everywhere function.
Now we have mentioned in the morning
that the automatic four-sided painting function
is now optimized.
So now we are using the automatic four-sided painting function
when we use the automatic four-sided painting function.
One is that the four sides of the portion line
of the figure line
will be kept as much as possible.
Now we have the auto-close function.
Before binding to Google, we can choose to create a cover first.
The auto-close function can hide some places we don't want to see inside.
For example, the sleeve position.
After we use the auto-close function,
we define the closed area,
and the inner grid will be covered,
so it won't show up anymore.
When we bind to Google,
it won't show up anymore,
and the inner grid will be covered.
The other function is the same.
We can create a closed area,
so the inner grid won't show up anymore.
It also helps us save some face numbers.
In the everywhere function,
we can manually hide the cover.
We have used the auto-close function before.
After using the auto-close function,
we can see the gray grid area
is the area where the cover has been created.
We can also manually create a cover,
whether it is the front or the back,
we can choose whether to create a cover or not.
I will quickly skip the part of creating a cover.
After that, we can manually input.
We want to save the cover,
so we save the cover,
and the number of the cover.
I hope that the cover has the desired face number,
and we can input the number of the cover.
Then we can save the cover
according to the number of the cover
we input from the 3D window and 2D panel.
Then we can start the auto-close.
Although I didn't show the virtual model here,
we can see it in the background.
After the auto-close,
After the automatic binding is completed, we can start to adjust the effect of these bindings.
After we have finished the binding, we can brush the fist.
Because our fist is automatically brushed up,
you can also manually adjust the fist of our costume or model binding.
For example, you can increase the fist of a certain part,
or reduce the fist of a certain part between it and a specific joint.
All of these functions are hidden in the Everywhere function.
These bindings include reducing the fist of a certain part,
or smoothing the fist of a certain part of a certain joint.
They include the fist of multiple joints.
In addition, there is the Marker function.
This Marker function is similar to the Marker tool set in 3D printing.
It is similar to the Marker tool set in 3D printing.
In addition, we can adjust the position of the fist of a certain part of a certain joint.
For example, we can remove some grid lines or even out unnecessary fold lines.
During the adjustment, there may be some mismatches between the costume and the model.
We can fix these mismatches with the brush.
For example, we can fix the mismatches between the costume and the model.
We just need to fix it with the repair brush.
Now we are done with the material.
Before we create the UV,
we can set up some UVs.
For example, the number of pixels,
or the space between UVs.
After that, we can move on to the UV arrangement.
After arranging the UVs,
we can apply the material.
After applying the material,
we can create the UVs and UVs.
After that,
we can use the Everywhere function
to create a nice look.
Next, let's take a look at the materials
and the components.
First, after adding a new set of clothes,
we will have a list of materials
that will be added to this set of clothes.
So now we can create a list of materials
in Publish Designer.
In addition, because we are updating the GPU simulation,
the GPU simulation can quickly identify
multiple layers of clothes.
So now, whether we are doing animation
or clothing simulation,
we can directly use the GPU simulation
instead of using the CPU simulation.
In addition, in the new version,
when we are adjusting the material,
the following material groups will also be changed.
Now we will more objectively choose
different material groups
and separate them.
For example, the material text,
such as the French text,
or the texture.
As for the texture,
in the previous version,
we only had the color removal function
to adjust the texture.
Now, we will have the color change function.
For example, this base pattern
has a certain color,
but I want to change its color.
In the previous version,
we used the color removal function.
Now, we can directly change the color.
It does not affect the original color
and the distribution of the pattern.
I can change the color of a certain part of it.
In addition,
we also have the PVR generator.
It will automatically extract
what we need to use
from the basic pattern of the guide.
Whether it is the graphics,
or the transparency,
or the reflection,
or the metal pattern,
it can be automatically extracted
and generated.
Now, we can not only edit
the front pattern,
but also the opposite pattern
can be adjusted
and edited directly
in the 2D window.
Now, in our new
PVR generator,
in the previous version,
we changed the pattern
according to the texture used by it.
When the square face is still the UV pattern,
we changed it at the bottom.
If we change it to a unified UV form,
when we adjust the UV shell
in our UV editor,
it will change to a different
fabric texture.
Now, we can change it at the side of the fabric
to use the square face
or the same UV pattern.
Since you have talked about the update of the UV,
we can take a look at this.
All these patterns
that we will use
are all made of material.
Now, in our new PVR generator,
if we turn on the
the UV on the back
will be displayed.
We can adjust the UV
on the back of the panel.
In addition to adjusting the UV
on the back,
we can now support
the UV on the side of the panel.
Of course, if you turn on
the UV on the back,
the UV on the back
will not be turned off.
Now, we can see that
the UV on the side
has a thin line.
This will add the thickness
of the fabric itself
and the rendering thickness
of the panel.
So, if we increase
the thickness of the fabric
on the side,
we can see that
the UV on the side
has widened.
Now, we can
adjust the UV on the back.
By using UV
we can easily adjust
the UV on the back.
Now, we have the
application function.
We can add the
print function
on the fabric.
The difference between
the print function
and the application function
is that
although it can adjust
the value of these parameters,
like its shift
rate,
or its rotation,
these basic values
are the same
as adding them
to a panel.
But, they can't
adjust the strength
of the base pattern.
Theoretically,
in addition to
the print function,
there is a print function
to adjust the base pattern,
the bottom layer of the pattern.
The print function
is called as the graph.
For example, I have added a new texture.
As you can see, the texture will be directly assigned to the object window.
I can adjust the texture to all the textures you use.
I can also let the texture blend with the texture on the bottom layer.
It will use the texture on the bottom layer.
I can also let the texture on the top layer blend with the texture on the bottom layer.
It is also convenient for us to adjust the texture and the texture.
Now I can also display the hair in the 3D window.
In the new version, we have added the hair display function in the 3D window.
When we set the hair for a texture,
we can preview the hair effect in the lingu raise Video.
After using the hair effect, we can adjust the number of hair now and then.
For example, we can adjust its length, thickness, and anything in our hair.
It keeps us up to date and science effects.
It keeps up with everything and everything we do in our hair,
like this heel,
We can also adjust the hair in the Marble Designer editor.
You may be curious that there is no rendering function in MD,
or how to export the hair.
Now, the USD material type is able to export the number of hair settings.
So you can create hair in Marble Designer,
and export it via USD.
The next step is to update the material and accessories.
In MD, I just made a panel using a board.
After we define the panel as a button,
we can use different settings.
For example, I can set the same color as the button part,
and set the other light-colored line as the button line.
This way, my button has two components.
I can separate them.
I can separate the color of the line and the color of the button.
When I define the color,
you can see the size of the button in the window on the right.
Of course, we can also set the size of the button.
For example, after I set the color of the button,
I have defined the button body and the line.
So when I change the button,
I can also separate the color of the button,
and the color of the button.
You can see that I have a white panel in MD.
In fact, sometimes when we make this kind of component or button,
I will put it in a transparent panel.
In the future, I will change this white panel to a transparent material.
After that, this button will be attached to the panel,
and it can follow us to complete the animation recording.
Since we are talking about animation,
before we start,
I can talk about the new function of MD.
The new function is IK joint printing.
First of all, in the new MD,
our model supports IK joint points.
So when we adjust the position of the model,
we can directly use IK joint points to complete it.
For example, we have already saved the model of Everwear
and saved the frame.
It has no IK joint points to use.
So in the new MD,
we can directly use the function of IK joint printing
to print a set of IK joint points to it.
After that, we can start to adjust it freely
by using the IK joint function to adjust its position.
But if we have an external model,
it is animated,
we can now also bring the external model
with this set of animations
to define it as an action file
that matches the default model in the MD.
By automatically changing the action function,
we can choose to match this set of actions
to the selected gender or age model.
For example, now I am going to match
a female model identified in the MD.
After matching, you will see
that because its matching speed is very fast,
the action of the model just now
can be directly transferred to the model in the MD.
For example, now I have an identified model
that is wearing the set of IK joint points
that I made before.
Then I can add the action of the model
that has been transferred to the model in the MD.
In the new MD,
our GPU simulation
has improved the resolution of the simulation.
So now,
when we are doing animation,
we can also choose to use GPU
to complete the simulation.
So we can see that
our actual resolution speed is very fast.
So now, when we are doing animation,
we can also use GPU to complete the simulation.
This can help us save time
in the workflow.
Since we have talked about these animations,
let's take a look at the update
on the key point animation.
In the new MD,
we can create key points
for many attributes.
For example, our virtual model
can choose to use the key point animation
to create the key point.
Now I am a T-Pose virtual model.
There is a key point of the joint here.
I can give it a key point here.
After adding the key point,
because we have just used
the IK joint function,
we can make some adjustments
to its posture.
When we drag it to the back,
we can find the appropriate
key point number.
Then we can load the action
and the posture.
After loading the posture,
we can click here
and give it a key point.
Later,
or when you are doing animation,
from T-Pose or A-Pose
to the first point,
you can also use this method
to complete its transition animation.
Because in the past,
people would say that transition animation
is too fast.
Or I want to tolerate
that transition animation,
we can also use the key point tool
to make the middle line change.
This helps us
to make the virtual model
in good clothes
more consistent
when it becomes
the first action.
Of course,
we can also manually
adjust the position
of the joints
and record the key point.
For example,
my outfit just now,
now my model
has been transformed
by the key point.
When I was doing the animation,
I found that
some parts of it
are not in harmony with the hand.
That's because
when we are doing the animation,
if the bending is too high,
it doesn't match
the bending
of other pieces.
When the height
is too high,
it may not match
the bending of other pieces.
So,
we can use the key point
to make the bending
match the bending
of the virtual model.
After that,
we can also use
the key point
tool
for the single key point
tool.
For example,
now,
the key point tool
allows the material
to move
along with the hand.
But,
when I reach
a certain position,
the key point tool
is not used
anymore.
So,
we can use
the key point tool
to find out
whether the key point
tool
is activated
or not.
At the beginning,
the key point tool
is activated
because I need
the key point tool
to move along
with my hand.
So,
I can use
the key point tool
when the key point tool
is activated.
After that,
when I am doing
the hand transformation
or other movements,
when I don't need
the key point tool
anymore,
I can use
the key point tool
to activate
the other key point tool
and then
the key point tool
to activate
the key point tool.
After that,
let's take a look.
At the beginning,
the key point tool
doesn't move
along with my hand.
When I take out
the material,
the key point tool
doesn't follow
my hand anymore.
It won't stick
to my hand.
So,
when we are doing
special effects
or when we need
animation,
we can use
the key point tool
to activate
the key point tool.
And the wind control
is also
able to activate
the key point tool.
At the beginning, I will select the position where the wind blows, and then I will adjust the intensity of the wind to match the position of the wind.
The position of the wind is actually a linear change in the middle.
Of course, you can also choose not to make a linear change, which is to automatically change the position of the wind when the wind jumps directly.
But what I am using here is the linear change setting.
Then you will see that because of the rotation and the position of the wind, the direction of the wind is actually adjusted.
This is the key point of our wind control device.
The previous version of the wind control device's key point is not that the single attribute can also hit the key point.
But now we can hit the key point of the single attribute, which can make more controllable adjustments to our wind creation.
After I hit the key point of the wind control device, I will go back to the animation again to see if there is anything I want to adjust.
Then, I also hit the key point of the cherry blossom flower pot that I made before.
This is our current material.
When you use the fabric physics attribute, you can also hit the key point of its fabric physics attribute.
What I am doing here is to hit the key point of its weight.
So at the beginning, the speed of the flower pot to float is relatively slow.
Then, because of its density, the speed of the flower pot to float will be faster.
So in the new version, you can try to hit the key point of the fabric physics attribute of your different pieces.
Your expression can raise the faster speed to a lower speed to create a different effect.
Ok, in order to make it more obvious, I am also hitting the key of its fabric.
The fabric's plastic material is somewhat settled down, then the leaves become red.
Because the material will drop and tremble when we turn the ahoraDon.
the color will change, so be careful.
The physical attribute will record the color lose in our animation.
As you can see, the left side of the figure is also very fast.
This is done by the physical properties adjustment.
The last one is the rendering of the model picture.
In the new version,
our Mammoth 3.3 supports the rendering of the model picture.
For example, in the 3D window,
if I want to see a 3D effect or a rendering effect,
we can first set the parameters we want.
For example, the roughness of the lines,
such as the grain line, the rendering line, and the internal line,
the roughness of their colors can be adjusted.
If you want to put the files in your asset folder,
you can also use this function.
It's very convenient.
You can also choose to display the material of the costume,
or display the single color of the costume.
You can also use the quick photo function in the 3D window
to show the rendering of the model picture.
The final model picture shows the rendering of the quick photo.
You can use it as our cover picture,
or display the model picture.
I hope you like this video.
Now I am going to show you the software that I use in this case.
I will share you some of the software that I use now.
I will also share some of the software that I use in the new model picture.
When we are done,
Mammoth 3.3 will be available.
You can watch it.
Thank you very much.